各位
Everyone...
这是亚伦
this is Aaron.
我们在外面碰见了他 只有他一人
We met him outside. He's by himself.
我们拿走了他的武器和装备
We took his weapons and we took his gear.
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you.
你说他有武器
You said he had a weapon?
你需要什么吗
There something you need?
他在附近有营地
He has a camp nearby.
他想要我们去面试加入
He wants us to audition for membership.
真希望能用个别的词
I wish there was another word.
面试让我们听起来像是个舞蹈团
Audition makes it sound like we're some kind of a dance troupe.
我们只在周五晚上跳舞
That's only on Friday nights.
而且那不是营地
Um, and it's not a camp.
而是社区
It's a community.
我觉得你们都会成为很有价值的一员
I think you all would make valuable additions.
但这轮不到我来决定
But it's not my call.
我的任务就是说服你们跟我回家
My job is to convince you all to follow me back home.
我知道
I know.
如果我是你 我也不会去
If I were you, I wouldn't go either.
除非我知道我去的是什么地方
Not until I knew exactly what I was getting into.
萨沙 你能把我的包给瑞克吗
Sasha, can you hand Rick my pack?
前面的口袋里有个信封
Front pocket, there's an envelope.
光靠嘴上说我们的社区
There's no way I could convince you to come with me
是没法说服你们跟我走的
just by talking about our community.
所以我带来了那些东西
That's why I brought those.
照片很不清楚 我提前道歉
I apologize in advance for the picture quality.
- 我们刚发现旧相机店… - 没人在乎
- We just found an old camera store last... - Nobody gives a shit.
你说的太对了
You're absolutely 100% right.
那是我想给你们看的第一张照片
That's the first picture I wanted to show you
因为我说的社区的一切情况都不重要
because nothing I say about our community will matter
除非你们知道那里很安全
unless you know you'll be safe.
如果你加入我们 你会很安全
If you join us, you will be.
那面墙的每块板子
Each panel in that wall
都是长达15英尺 宽达12英尺的
is a 15-foot-high, 12-foot-wide
脱氧钢板
slab of solid steel
框架是冷轧钢梁和方形管
framed by cold-rolled steel beams and square tubing.
没有我们的允许 活人或行尸都无法进入
Nothing alive or dead gets through that without our say-so.
如我所说 安全显然很重要
Like I said, security is obviously important.
实际上 只有一项资源
In fact, there's only one resource
对我们社区的生存而言更加重要
more critical to our community's survival.
那就是人
The people.
我们同心协力 十分强大
Together we're strong.
你们能让我们更强大
You can make us even stronger.
下一张照片是门里的情况
The next picture, you'll see inside the gates.
我们的社区建于…
Our community was first construc...
《行尸走肉》
我说清楚
So we're clear,
我的表情并不是说"我们攻击这人吧"
that look wasn't a "Let's attack that man" look.
而是"在我看来他这个人不错"
It was a "He seems like an okay guy to me" look.
我们得绑住他 清空他的包
We got to secure him. Dump his pack.
- 看看他到底是个什么样的人 - 瑞克
- Let's see what this guy really is. - Rick.
其余人 我们需要眼观六路
Everybody else, we need eyes in every direction.
他们来找我们了
They're coming for us.
我们不知道他们如何来 何时来
We might not know how or when,
但是他们一定会来
but they are.
我和萨沙开始没看见他
Me and Sasha, we didn't see him.
如果他想伤害我们早就下手了
If he had wanted to hurt us, he could've.
有人发现什么了吗
Anybody see anything?
藏身之地太多了
Just a lot of places to hide.
继续观察
All right, keep looking.
你找到了什么
What did you find?
从没见过这种枪
Never seen a gun like that before.
那记右交叉拳真厉害 瑞克
That's a hell of a right cross there, Rick.
扶他坐起来
Sit him up.
- 我觉得最好… - 没事
- I think it's better if... - It's okay.
他没事 扶他坐起来
He's fine. Sit him up.
你小心谨慎
You're being cautious.
我完全理解
I completely understand.
你们来了多少人
How many of your people are out there?
你有一把信号枪 可以向同伙发信号
You have a flare gun. You have it to signal your people.
来了多少人
How many of them are there?
- 这重要吗 - 是的
- Does it matter? - Yes.
很重要
Yes, it does.
我是说 当然了
I mean, of course,
我们来了多少人 这的确很重要
it matters how many people are actually out there,
但是 就算我说了人数又能怎样呢
but does it matter how many people i tell you are out there?
因为我敢肯定 不管我说多少人
Because I'm pretty sure no matter what number I say...
8个
eight,
32个
32,
444个
444,
没人
zero...
不管我说什么 你都不会信我
no matter what I say, you're not going to trust me.
脸上被打了一拳
Well, it's hard to trust anyone
还笑得出来的人的确很难信任
who smiles after getting punched in the face.
那在路上给你们留下水的人呢
How about a guy who leaves bottles of water for you in the road?
你们跟踪我们多久了
How long you people been following us?
时间长到发现了你们基本上无视了
Long enough to see that you practically ignore
身后跟着一群行尸
a pack of roamers on your trail.
长到发现了虽然你们没有食物和水
Long enough to see that despite a lack of food and water,
但也没有攻击彼此
you never turned on each other.
你们是幸存者
You're survivors
而且你们是有人性的人
and you're people.
如我所说 我希望
Like I said, and I hope
我再说一次时你不要打我
you won't punch me for saying it again,
人是世界上最重要的资源
that is the most important resource in the world.
你们来了多少人
How many others are out there?
一个
One.
我就知道你不会信我
I knew you wouldn't believe me.
如果言语和照片说服不了你
If it's not words, if it's not pictures,
你要怎么才能相信
what would it take to convince you
这是真的
that this is for real?
如果我开车带你们去社区呢
What if I drove you to the community?
你们所有人
All of you?
我们现在走 中午就能到
We leave now, we'll get there by lunch.
我不确定我们15个人怎么坐得下
I'm not sure how the 15 of us are going to fit
你和你那个朋友开来的那辆车
in the car you and your one friend drove down here in.
我们开了两辆车 如果我们发现了一队人
We drove separately. If we found a group,
我们希望能把他们都带回家
we wanted to be able to bring them all home.
我们都可以坐得下
There's enough room for all of us.
车就停在几英里外 对吗
And you're parked just a couple miles away, right?
山脊路东边 刚下16号公路
East on Ridge Road, just after you hit Route 16.
我们想停得更近 但是暴风雨来了
We wanted to get them closer, but then the storm came,
堵塞了道路 我们没办法清理
blocked the road. We couldn't clear it.
你编得真好
Yeah, you've really thought this through.
瑞克 如果我想埋伏你
Rick, if I wanted to ambush you,
我就袭击这里了
I'd do it here.
趁你们睡觉时点燃谷仓
You know, light the barn on fire while you slept,
你们从唯一的出口跑出时射杀你们
pick you off as you ran out the only exit.
你可以信任我
You can trust me.
我去看看车
I'll check out the cars.
没有什么车
There aren't any cars.
只有一个方法能知道
There's only one way to find out.
- 我们没必要知道 - 有的
- We don't need to find out. - We do.
你有自己的想法 你很确定
You know what you know and you're sure of it,
但我不确定
but I'm not.
我也不确定
Me neither.
你这样做很危险 还是听我的保险
Your way is dangerous, mine isn't.
难道有好地方我们偏不去
Passing up someplace where we can live?
也不让朱迪斯去吗
Where Judith can live?
这样才真的是危险
That's pretty dangerous.
我们必须一探究竟
We need to find out what this is.
我们能照顾好自己
We can handle ourselves.
所以我们一定要去看看
So that's what we're gonna do.
那我也去
Then I will, too.
我去
I'll go.
亚伯拉罕
Abraham.
行
Yeah.
我陪他们
I'll walk with them.
罗西塔
Rosita?
好的
Okay.
如有不测 弹药充足吗
If there's trouble, you got enough firepower?
就剩下手里这些了
We got what we got.
对讲机没电了
The walkies are out of juice.
若你们一小时后还没回来 我们就去支援
If you're not back in 60 minutes, we'll come.
说不定这样恰好中了别人的圈套
Which might be just what they want.
如果我们聚在一处 就是活靶子
If we're all in here, we're a target.
外面交给我
I've got the area covered.
好 两人一组 在附近隐蔽起来
All right, groups of two, find somewhere safe within eyeshot.
在世界还没乱套前
When the world was still the world,
我为非政府组织工作
I worked for an NGO.
我们的任务是往尼日尔河三角洲地区
Our mission was to deliver medicine and food
运送药品和食物
to the Niger River Delta.
坏人隔三差五就想取我性命
Bad people pointed guns in my face every other week.
你们不是坏人
You're not bad people.
你们不会杀我们
You're not going to kill us.
我们也绝不会杀你们
And we are definitely not going to kill you.
虽然我们是好人
Just because we're good people
不代表就不会杀你
doesn't mean we won't kill you.
若他们五人一小时后还没回来
If the five of them aren't back in an hour...
我就一刀捅穿你的脑袋
I'll put a knife in the base of your skull.
各位提高警惕 武器准备好
Eyes open, everybody. Weapons up.
一旦有人靠近就开枪
You see someone coming at us, you fire.
收到
Copy that.
只要看到人就开枪吗
So if we see someone, we just shoot them?
问得好
It's a good question.
如果他们跟我们一样呢
What if they're someone like us?
如果亚伦说的是实话呢
What if Aaron is telling the truth?
如果他们真的毫无恶意呢
What if they're someone who has nothing to do with this?
我们五个全副武装
We're five people walking with guns.
谁会没事跑来问好
No one's coming up to say hello.
但他就跑来问好了
But that's exactly what happened.
如果他们跟我们一样 我们更应该感到害怕
If it's someone like us, we should be afraid of them.
他不是说一直监视着我们吗
He said he was watching us, right?
那他昨天肯定看到我们了
It means he saw us yesterday.
既然他知道我们做过什么
And after everything we've done,
为什么还想让我们加入
why would he want us to join his group?
因为我们救了神父
People like us saved a priest.
救了跟总督一起去监狱的那个女孩
Saved a girl who rolled up up to the prison with the Governor.
还救了拿刀的疯女人
Saved a crazy lady with a sword.
他都看到了
He saw that.
我可不晓得他看到了什么
I don't know what he saw.
你看到我背包里的那瓶苹果酱了吧
You did see the jar of applesauce in my bag, right?
我不想耍花招
This isn't a trick.
我不想借此让你对我有好感
This isn't about trying to make you like me.
这是自卫本能
It's self-preservation.
如果行尸们循着哭声过来
Because if the roamers hear her and come this way,
我肯定先死
I know I'll be the first to go.
你觉得我会毒害你的女儿吗
You think I'm trying to poison your baby daughter?
我被绑着 而你又决心
I'm tied up and you've already expressed
要捅穿我的脑袋
a willingness to stab me in the head.
如果我残忍地杀了你的女儿
How would cruelly killing your daughter in front of you
对我有什么好处
in any way help the situation?
也许她死不了 只是会生病
Maybe she doesn't die. Maybe she gets sick.
也许只有你能帮她 那我就输了
Maybe you're the only one that can help her and I just lose.
的确只有我可以帮她
I am the only one who can help her
因为我有苹果酱 这叫双赢
because I have applesauce and we all win.
我讨厌苹果酱
I hate applesauce.
我妈常逼我吃我讨厌的食物
My mom used to make me eat foods
说吃了就能变得更爷们儿
I didn't like to make me more manly.
鲑鱼肉饼 苹果酱 洋葱之类的
Salmon patties, applesauce, and onions.
她那时很迷惑 尽了最大的努力改变我
She was a very confused woman who tried her damndest.
我带来苹果酱是想表明我们那有苹果树
I just bring the jar to show that we have apple trees nearby.
就像你说的 要死也你先死
Like you said, you'll be the first to go.
那个社区足够大
The community is big enough.
我们可以给你找到安身之处
We can find a place for you to live
即使她哭闹
where even when she cries, no one,
也不会传到墙外
nothing can hear it outside the walls.
你还有43分钟
You got 43 minutes.
他说的是实话
He was telling the truth.
给我站住 混蛋
Not one step closer, asshole!
我来搞定
I got 'em.
一起上吧
We got 'em.
该死
Damn it!
多谢
Thanks.
安全吗
All clear?
安全
All clear.
我的个乖乖
Gracious Ignatius.
好久没吃过了
Oh, it has been a while.
我见过雷克斯一晚上吃了三罐
I think I saw Rex eat three cans one night.
四罐
Four.
那混蛋知道如果他不丢过来
Son of a bitch knew if he didn't toss 'em back,
我就要去抢了
I'd have come for 'em.
在消防车那会儿
Back at the fire truck,
我打了尤金
after Eugene...
你是不是以为我也会打你
did you think I was gonna hurt you?
没有
No.
那时你不理智
It's not you.
这些 现在是我们的了
This, this is ours now.
我们还有很多
There's more than enough.
不管我们去不去你的营地 这些都归我们
It's ours whether or not we go to your camp.
什么意思 我们为什么不去
What do you mean? Why wouldn't we go?
他也许在撒谎
If he were lying
或者想伤害我们
or if he wanted to hurt us...
但他没撒谎
but he isn't
也没有伤害我们
and he doesn't.
我们需要这地方
We need this.
所以我们全都要去
So we're going, all of us.
有人有不同意见吗
Somebody say something if they feel differently.
我不知道该怎么说
I don't know, man.
这个谷仓一股子马粪味儿
This barn smells like horse shit.
那我们走
We're going.
我们往哪走 你的营地在哪
So where are we going? Where's your camp?
每次带新成员回去
Well, every time I've done this,
都是由我来驾车的
I've been behind the wheel driving recruits back.
我相信你们是好人
I believe you're good people.
对此我敢赌上性命
I've bet my life on it.
我只是还不敢赌上我朋友们的性命
I'm just not ready to bet my friends' lives just yet.
你不能驾车
You're not driving.
如果你想回家 就说出路线
So if you want to get home, you'll have to tell us how.
向北走16号公路
Go north on Route 16.
然后呢
And then?
到了我再告诉你们
I'll tell you when we get there.
我们向北走23号公路
We'll take 23 north.
到那里以后你再给我们指路
You'll give us directions from there.
那…我不知道还能怎么说
That's... I don't know how else to say it...
这是个糟糕的主意
that's a bad idea.
我们清理了16号公路
We've cleared 16.
走那里更快
It'll be faster.
我们走23号公路
We'll take 23.
我们日落时出发
We leave at sundown.
我们要走夜路吗
We're doing this at night?
听着 我知道这很危险
Look, I know it's dangerous.
但要比白天开到他们门前去好多了
But it's better than riding up to the gates during the day.
如果有危险 我们就必须
If it isn't safe, we need to get gone
在他们察觉之前离开
before they know we're there.
我们不会伤害你们的
No one is going to hurt you.
你想保护你的人
You're trying to protect your group,
但其实是置他们于危险之中
but you're putting them in danger.
告诉我营地在哪 我们现在就走
Tell me where the camp is, we'll leave right now.
今晚肯定很漫长
It's going to be a long night.
吃东西吧
Eat.
能休息就休息一下
Get some rest if you can.
我想 你 我和格伦开车带他一起走
I'm thinking you, me, and Glenn drive with that guy.
卡尔和朱迪思坐在那辆车上更安全
Carl and Judith are safer in there.
你没事吧
You okay?
你刚才说我们现在就走
When you said that we were going,
是真心的吗
was that for real?
还是说 你只想骗他说出营地在哪
Or are you just trying to get this guy to tell you where his camp is?
我们要去
We're going.
你是指不论付出什么代价
Whatever it takes to get there.
只要能到就行吗
Just as long as we get there.
你第一次靠近伍德伯里的外墙时
When you first came up on the walls outside Woodbury...
听到了什么
what did you hear?
没声音
Nothing.
终点站呢
And Terminus?
也没声音
Nothing.
今晚某时
Sometime tonight,
我们就会到他的营地墙边
we'll be outside his camp's walls.
在看不到里面的情况下
And without seeing inside,
我必须做出是否带家人进去的决定
I'm gonna have to decide whether to bring my family in.
他之前问过我 怎样我才会
He asked me before what it would take for me
相信他说的是真的
to believe it was real.
事实上
Truth is...
没有任何东西能说服我走进那里
I'm not sure if anything could convince me to go in there.
但是 我要去看看
But I'm gonna see.
我要去看看
I'm gonna see.
(北23号公路)
(马萨诸塞州)
(德克萨斯州)
我想集齐五十个州的车牌
Um, I'm trying to collect all 50 states.
都钉在我家的墙上
Put them all on a wall in my house.
你有自己的房子吗
You have your own house?
你可以自己看看
See for yourself.
为什么你没有你伙伴们的照片
Why don't you have any pictures of your people?
我拍过一张全体人员照片
Oh, I took a picture of the whole group,
但是曝光出了问题
but I didn't get the exposure right.
之后我想洗出那张照片时 它…
When I tried to develop it later, it just...
你问过他那些问题了吗
Did you ask him the questions?
没有
No.
你杀了多少行尸
How many walkers have you killed?
抱歉 什么
I'm sorry, what?
多少
How many?
我也不知道 很多吧
I don't know. A lot.
你杀了多少人
How many people?
两个
Two.
为什么
Why?
因为他们想杀我
Because they tried to kill me.
你窃听了我们吗
You were listening to us?
我说过我在监视你们 是的 我窃听了
I already said I was watching you. Yes, I was listening.
就是说他的同伙可能也有窃听器
It means his people could have one, too.
他们可能已经听到我们的计划了 有危险
They could've heard our plan. This isn't safe.
该死
Shit!
- 格伦 - 他们就在我们后面
- Glenn! - They were right behind us.
他们可能撞上我们 现在他们可以下车了
They would have hit us. Now they can get out.
我没看到他们
I don't see them.
不 他们走了 他们脱身了
No, they're gone. They got away.
好的 我们折回去找他们 走吧
All right, we'll circle back and find them. Let's go.
- 他们没事吧 - 没事
- They're okay? - Yeah.
好 我们上23号公路行驶几英里后往左拐
All right, we can take a left a couple of miles up 23.
- 到杰弗逊大道 - 杰弗逊大道
- Jefferson Avenue. - Jefferson Avenue.
我们得离开这里
We got to get out of here.
动啊
Come on.
我们得离开这里
We got to get out of here.
动啊 动啊
Come on. Come on.
我去看看怎么回事
Let me see what I can see.
它们冲着我们来了
They're coming right for us.
- 是的 我们知道 - 动啊 动啊
- Yeah, we know. - Come on, come on!
我们必须马上离开
We need to leave now.
等等
Hold on.
该死
Shit.
那是谁干的
Who did that?
我得走了 这件事结束了
I need to leave. This is over.
让我出去 我必须走了 这件事结束了
Let me out. I need to get outta here. It's over.
- 怎么回事 - 让我出去
- What's going on? - Let me out!
你们看到了吗
Did you see that?
米恩琼 别管他 我们得找到自己人
Michonne, leave him! We need to find our people.
他们看到了信号弹 肯定以为是我们放的
They saw that flare. They'll think we shot it.
去那边就能找到他们
This is how we find them.
格伦呢
Where's Glenn?
滚开
Get off!
想跑的话快跑吧
Run if you want.
我还有其他的事要担心
I got other things to worry about.
我们可以一起活下去
We can make it together.
但只有我们在一起才能活下去
But we can only make it together.
这是你说的 我是在窃听
You said that. I was listening.
格伦
Glenn!
他肯定在附近
He's got to be somewhere around here.
格伦
Glenn!
如果你想再把我绑起来 可以 但要快
If you really want to tie me up again, that's fine, but hurry up.
没时间了 我们走那边
There's no time. We're going that way.
他们在哪
Where are they?
我不知道
I don't know.
如果这是个陷阱 要把我们引回去
If this is a trap to get us back where you want us,
那你的人今晚就死定了
your people are going to die tonight.
信号弹是水塔那边放出的
The flare was towards the water tower.
爸爸
Dad!
- 你妹妹还好吗 - 没事 我们都很好
- Your sister okay? - Yeah. Yeah, we're fine.
埃里克 埃里克
Eric? Eric?
- 埃里克 - 我在里面
- Eric? - In here.
埃里克
Eric!
Eric?
我没事
I'm okay.
只是运动伤
It's like a volleyball injury.
脚踝骨折
It's a broken ankle.
至少玛姬是这样说的
At least that's what Maggie said.
我喜欢她
I like her.
不是大伤
It's not a big deal.
天呐
Oh, my God.
回去以后我去医务室看看就行
I'll just go to the infirmary when we get back.
当我看到信号弹时 我…
When I saw that flare go up, I...
我以为…
I thought...
你很担心我 是吗
You were worried, were you?
是的
Yeah.
这是你的错 你知道吗
This is your fault, you know?
是吗
Is that so?
因为我爱你
Because I love you.
我一担心就会做蠢事
And because when I'm worried, I do stupid things.
我一做蠢事就会藏到老破车底下
And when I do stupid things, I wind up underneath a rust bucket
被行尸包围着
surrounded by roamers
左脚踝还被后轮压了
who roll a rear passenger tire onto my left ankle.
今天也有好事
Hey, something good came out of today.
我等你的时候搜索了周围
While I was waiting for you, I searched through the neighborhood.
发现了这个
I found that.
你搞丢了车牌
You lost the license plates.
我把车都搞丢了
I lost the car.
也许这样更好
Maybe it's for the best.
说实话那车太难看了
That monstrosity out front can run.
丑得都能吓跑行尸
It's so ugly, it'll scare the roamers away.
我是埃里克
Hi. I'm Eric.
我是瑞克
Rick.
没事的
It's okay.
打搅一下 打搅一下
Excuse me. Excuse me.
各位
Everyone.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
你们救了埃里克
You saved Eric.
我欠你们所有人的
I owe you. All of you.
我会确保我们抵达社区以后
And I will make sure that debt is paid in full
完全报答你们的恩情
when we get to our community.
等我们抵达亚历山大以后
When we get to Alexandria.
现在 我不知道你们怎么想
Now, I'm not sure about you,
但是我今晚不想再坐车了
but I'd rather not do any more driving tonight.
也许我们可以明早再上路
Maybe we can hit the road tomorrow morning.
听起来不错
That sounds fine.
但是如果我们要在这里过夜
But if we're staying here for the night,
你就必须睡那边
you're sleeping over there.
你真觉得有这个必要吗
You really think we got to do that?
这样保险点 我们又不了解你
It's the safe play. We don't know you.
除非你枪杀我
The only way you're gonna stop
不然我一定要和他在一起
me from being with him right now is by shooting me.
瑞克 他告诉我们营地的位置了
Rick, he told us where the camp is.
而且他的同伴真的只有一人
And he really was only travelling with one other person.
他们都没有武器
They're both unarmed.
其中一个人脚踝还断了
One of them's got a broken ankle.
我也想让我们安全点
I want us to be safe, too.
我不能放弃一切人性
I can't give up everything else.
我知道我说过什么
I know what I said,
但是其实这很重要
but it does matter.
好吧
All right.
怎么了
Yeah?
我知道该吃药了
I know it's time for another dose,
但我想让他一路睡到家
but I want to let him sleep until we get home.
不 这是给你的
No, it's for you.
只是几瓶药 不用吝啬
A few bottles. Don't need to be stingy with 'em.
我知道那有多疼
I know how bad those hurt.
是啊
Yeah.
谢谢
Thank you.
你的腿
Oh, your leg.
在灾变前伤的吗
Did that happen before?
在灾变中伤的
During.
我爸和我出了车祸
Dad and me, car accident.
路上有行尸
Rotters in the road.
我以前有个医生
I had a doctor.
能走路已经很幸运了
Probably lucky I can even walk.
在亚历山大有一位很出色的外科医生
We have a pretty gifted surgeon in Alexandria.
他叫皮特
His name's Pete.
我见过他妙手回春
I've seen him do some amazing things.
他也许能帮你
He might be able to help.
是吗
Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
好吧
七张桩牌 方格棋盘
Seven-card stud. Stares and squares.
大小顺序是A K Q J
It's aces, cuatros, neeners, and two-eyed jacks.
一共14张外卡 你是认真的吗
So there's 14 wild cards? Are you serious?
跟两只在交配的狗一样认真
Serious as two copulating dogs.
亚伯拉罕
Abraham.
看
Look.
看路 壮汉
Eyes on the road, champ.
还有多远
How much longer we got?
只剩不到一半路了 为什么问
Looks like we're a little over halfway there. Why?
我们能做到的
We can make it.
做不到啊
Can't win.
跟那辆救火车没两样
Might as well paint it red, put a ladder on it.
我们只需要换个电池
All we need is another battery.
上哪儿去找电池啊
Where in the hell are we gonna find another battery?
来这边
Right over here.
你怎么知道那里有电池
How'd you know those were there?
来吧
Come on.
战斗结束了
The fight's over.
你必须学会放手
You've got to let it go.
我知道这很难
I know it's hard.
毕竟生存欲曾令你
After it's kept you...
温暖 饱餐
warm and fed and...
幸存
alive.
但是这也会
But the fight...
转变你
it turns on you.
你必须放手
You've got to let it go.
鲍勃在教堂也对我说过这话
That's what Bob was trying to tell me back at the church.
该冒什么险
What to risk.
何时是安全的
When it's safe.
何时该接纳他人
When to let someone in.
规矩一直在变
The rules keep changing.
对我来说是这样
They did for me.
在我们走之前 我要…
Before we get going, I got to...
我要去静静
I got to take a moment.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
是的
Yeah. Yeah.
亲爱的
Hey. Hey, sweetheart.
过来
Come here.
尽管你错了
Even though you were wrong,
但你那样做依然是对的
you were still right.
我们走吧
Should we go?